ALEXIS RAY



Enthusiastic High School SENIOR with 3 years of cashier and customer service experience. Seeking a fast-paced customer service role that will offer the chance to grow and learn more about the company and show off interpersonal and communication skills.

EDUCATION

High School Diploma | Steinbrenner High School

2020-2024 (GRADUATING MAY 23RD, 2024, LAST DAY IN CLASSES MAY 10TH)

4.1 WEIGHTED GPA

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Associate | Publix

06/2021 - CURRENT:

- Provide premier customer service, including greeting and assisting customers.
- Retrieve items and correct problems customers have
- Continuous interacting with customers and standing for long periods.
- Lifting up to 50lbs

Customer Service Cashier | Publix

06/2021-CURRENT:

- Handle Forms of cash and other tenders accurately and correctly
- Correctly weigh and scan products using POS
- Repetitive movements, engaging with customers while performing task
- Maintain a sanitary and organized workspace.

Verizon Job Shadow | Verizon

2024

- Understand company goals, how the service rooms work, project management, and day-to-day interactions in a professional company setting.

SKILLS:

CERTIFICATIONS:

- Customer Service and Assistance
- Cash Handling
- Problem Resolution
- Cashiering
- Safety Regulations
- Refund Processing
- Communication Skills

- Project Management (PMI)
- Entrepreneurship and Small Business
- Windows Operating Systems
- HTML and CSS
- User Interface Designer